"The Second" took over my sister's body and told me to look after you guys.
They also said not to tell you anything.
But you just told us...
Yeah.
I probably shouldn't have forced you to talk.
Did they mention what they'd do if you told us?
Well—
Ah...
Choosing you was a mistake.
Well, whatever.
It's time to say good-bye.
You're...
The Second?
I said that you'd regret it if you told them.
I said that I'd make it forever.
Remember?
Ow!
My clothes!
Aoki?!
Why?
It isn't five yet!
Clothes! My clothes!
Right! Clothes!
Just a minute!
Taichi?!
You, too?!
So the times are random now, too?
I'm hungry!
Okay, okay! Just get down from there, okay?
So this is how it feels to have your time regressed.
It's like I remember everything from elementary school.
It's past five.
This is happening because Taichi told us about The Second, right?
Sorry. It's my fault.
Don't apologize.
It's my fault, not yours.
Now we can't even go outside, let alone go home.
We probably can't keep quiet about this any longer.
Maybe we should tell our families or Gossan about—
No, we shouldn't!
I-I mean, I don't really want to trouble our families over this...
Right.
We don't know what'll happen if we tell anyone else.
Let's keep this a secret for as long as we can.
I think I can manage with just a phone call.
But my mom and sister are really mad at me right now.
It won't be pretty when I get back home.
Can I go home just for a little?
Is there something you're worried about?
I just wanted to talk to my mom a little.
Iori-chan, are you cold?
No, I'm fine.
Thank you very much for your consideration.
It's 11, and she still isn't back to normal.
I want to take a bath.
Yes.
I'd love to take a bath, too, but we can't right now, right?
I'll bear with it.
I didn't see!
I didn't see anything!
Did you just go back to normal?
Yeah, looks like it.
Sorry, I didn't mean to wake you.
What was I like when I was 11?
You were really calm and collected.
You seemed very mature.
Very mature, huh?
So that's how you saw me.
When your time regresses, your memories from back then are really clear, right?
Yeah.
It leaves you feeling guilty and regretful.
You can't help but think, "If only I did that,"
or, "Maybe I should've done that."
Aoki and Yui were amazing.
I don't think I'll ever be able to be like them.
I kind of felt the same way.
But aren't there some things you can do together with others that can't be done alone?
Do together, huh?
Like, I mean...
Hey, why are we even talking about this?
Let's get some sleep while we still can.
I told you, my friend suddenly offered to take me with her on vacation—
I'm sorry I didn't call you—
Huh? Oh, she's not here right now, but...
Sorry, I have to do something, so I'm hanging up now!
Sorry, Mom!
Not good.
She may just end up calling the police to search for us.
We're running out of options here.
There's nothing we can do about this.
Oh, sorry.
Hello, Mom?
Yeah.
Wait. Mom, what's wrong?
Mom!
Your second father?
Yeah.
Not too long ago, he came back, saying that he wanted to get back together with my mom.
Wait, what do you mean?
We've never heard about this.
Well...
He has his share of problems.
He's kind of violent.
He helped out around the house for a while after coming back, but lately...
Is it serious?
He doesn't harm us physically, but...
Sounds like a model bad parent to me.
Just kick him out already.
This could be our chance to do things differently.
There have been times where I thought,
"If I did things differently as a kid, maybe everything would have worked out better."
I mean, there are so many choices that I didn't make.
And it looks like the ones I chose were wrong.
My mom just said not to come home tonight.
Why didn't you tell us?!
Because...
it's my problem.
Hello, Mom?
Dad...
Wait, don't—
Hold on—
What should I do?
What should I do?!
I have to go!
But I can't go!
But I have to!
What should I do?
Calm down, Nagase!
Iori—
H-Hold on, where are you going?
Home.
Why?
I gotta protect my mom.
If I do things right, Dad won't be mad.
Why do you have to protect her?
Because I love Mom.
Huh?
Did my... time regress?
How long has it been?
It was only for a minute.
So how old...
How old...
I remember now.
Huh? Why?
Sorry.
I know I'm being stupid, but I have to go.
Wait, Nagase!
Iori!
Iori-chan!
I won't cause you any trouble.
I'll do this by myself.
Stop right there, you idiot!
You messed up when you were a kid, right?
Do you know why?
It's because you didn't tell anyone, didn't depend on anyone, and tried to do everything yourself.
I...
You kept it all to yourself, and now it's come to this,
but you're still trying to do everything by yourself.
You really think it'll work out this time?
But...
Take a look around you.
Who do you see?
But this is something personal, so...
No, it—
No, it's not!
If you're suffering, then it's our problem, too!
Though, on second thought, it really is something personal...
Taichi, stop talking.
If you're worried, tell someone.
Don't keep it to yourself and do something stupid.
You told me that, you know.
I've always thought
that I had to do it all by myself.
It's my fault it turned out this way, after all.
So... I...
Iori-chan, just keep it simple.
He's right, Iori.
You just need to say one thing.
We're always right beside you.
Will you help me?
Shouldn't we take the train or the bus?
If we're lucky, no one's time'll get regressed.
You're being too optimistic.
Aoki!
See what I mean?
What should we do? Do we take him with us?
I'll stay with him.
We'll follow once Aoki's back to normal.
Yui...
Go. It's okay.
We're here.
This is my home.
So what do we do now?
Should we go in with you?
Mom!
Open the door! It's me!
Please! Open the door! Mom!
Shut up!
I'm coming! Hold your horses!
Dammit!
Should we go in by ourselves?
We don't know the situation.
What if we go in there and make things worse?
But we don't know how long Nagase's going to be like this.
Oh my.
It looks like you're in quite the fix.
Why are you showing yourself now?!
Are you behind this mess after all?
No, I'm not.
But there's something I need to do first.
Huh?
What's going...
Huh? My arm isn't in my sleeve...
Was my time regressed again?
Balloon Vine?!
This marks the end of this phenomenon.
I wasn't responsible for this one.
You weren't?
So you and The Second were acting separately?
Well, we aren't a single consciousness.
The one you call "The Second" has their own ideas.
But I've made sure they won't meddle in your affairs again.
Regardless, it's all over now.
What about my mom?
What happened to my mom?
Your time was regressed, so we had to run.
We should go back right now.
Oh, I have a suggestion for you, Nagase-san.
What?
I don't have time for you right now.
Nagase-san, would you do anything differently?
It seems I've caused you quite a bit of trouble because I wasn't involved.
So I thought I'd do something nice for you as an apology.
I'll undo everything that's happened until now
and let you relive everything from whenever you want.
You mean you'll take Iori back in time, and she'd relive her life from there?
But...
But there's no way to...
You know you can't do anything about it now, don't you, Nagase-san?
What do you mean?
I'm talking about your current situation.
I can't do anything about it now?
Would you do anything differently?
There's no way to...
I've always wanted to be my true self.
Not any of the "me's" I pretended were me.
If I did things differently,
my mom might have been happier.
Maybe I wouldn't have caused trouble for anyone.
I...
So, I...
I love you just the way you are, Nagase.
We all love you just the way you are.
Yaegashi-san, Inaba-san.
Could I ask you to keep quiet?
You're the one who decides, Nagase-san.
I am who I am now because of my past.
Calling any choice I made a mistake would be calling who I am now a mistake.
I don't want to do that.
I can't do something like that after watching how Yui and Aoki live their lives to the fullest.
I wouldn't be here if I hadn't lived my past the way I did.
So I wouldn't do anything differently.
All right, then.
That settles it.
You can go now.
Let's get going.
Iori...
Are you sure we can just sit around like this?
Yes. I don't think he'll be back for a while.
Come on, Iori.
Isn't there something you want to ask her?
That's why we came here.
Iori-chan, just keep it simple.
Okay.
What do you want to ask?
Mom, do you love him? Does he make you happy?
No.
There was a time when I did love him, but I don't now.
Then why are you letting him stay here?
I had a feeling that you were trying to find something again.
Were you?
No, I wasn't.
Well...
Maybe I was...
I wanted to do things differently...
See?
But that was for you!
Huh?
Excuse me,
but have you ever talked this through?
No.
All I cared about was if my mom was happy.
I didn't mind putting up with him if it meant my daughter was happy.
Mom, I can't be happy if you're not happy!
Iori...
Really?
The hell's the door locked for?!
Open the hell up, woman!
He's home!
Should we call the police?
It'll be six on one. We'll be fine, won't we?
Open up, dammit!
This is for me to handle.
But Mom...
Hurry it up!
I'll be fine.
Hey!
Shut up!
Huh?!
I've put up with you for long enough!
Who says I have to let you in?!
What, you—
Hit the road!
I can't—
And don't come back!
You worthless bum!
That was crazy!
I've never seen my mom like that.
But it turned out really well.
He promised he'd never come back.
Yeah. And he was crying on his hands and knees by the end.
But you whispered "Thanks" to him, didn't you?
Yeah.
Sure, he might've been pretty bad,
but I am who I am now because he was there.
I thought, "Hey, you need to at least thank him for that much!"
I can't say I'm really and truly thankful,
but if I held a grudge, I'd be stuck in the past.
Forgiving him helped me to move on.
You...
You guys are the reason I'm here now.
Thanks.
Sorry about all the trouble.
No, you don't need to apologize.
I went overboard, too.
Suddenly challenging you to a fight was going way too far.
Right?
So that match didn't count!
What?
So I've still never lost to you.
And that's a fact.
You quit karate, but you still hate losing.
About that...
I think I'm going to pick up karate again.
I'm going to start going to a dojo again.
The next time we fight, it'll be at nationals!
Oh, shoot! Can I get your phone number, Chinatsu?
Oh, sure, Yui!
And so, our winter break ended,
and our lives went back to normal.
We didn't know how things would go,
but we put our heads together and got through it.
I really think that the CRC is amazing.
Of course, we don't know when or if Balloon Vine will come back to stir things up.
But as long as we're together, we can get through it.
That's what I believe.
Everyone helped me again this time.
Whenever Balloon Vine does something,
everyone around me helps me through it.
I think the CRC is really amazing.
Especially Taichi.
I owe Taichi more than you could imagine.
Taichi is a great guy.
He's a great guy, but...
Do I really love Yaegashi Taichi?